We have rebuilt this park quite a lot.
Now you see that the lighting is completely different.
We have even lighting that spreads lighting throughout the park.
This is the same time of day as the last picture.
But the lighting has done wonders with how we can see each other.
There are really no dark spots in this park at all.
Look at the bush and the height of the bush.
No one can hide with ease behind these bush.
We have an inviting park that invites you to spontaneous activities.
Has drug crime, which we see has decreased drastically.
Now that we have made this change in the park, we get much fewer reports of insecurity in the park in the evening.
We see that drug crime has almost disappeared from the scene.
Then we have to ask ourselves: Has the crime moved on?
Has it been printed to surrounding areas?
What we do now we are also following up and studying neighborhoods all around.
After the effort in the park.
Has the problems with drug traffic increased around?
Then we have support that we only pushed the crime away from the scene.
Which may have similar problems.
To see if the same problems do not change because they do not rebuild the park.
And see if we get a change when we rebuild the park.
That we have a control area.
Then we get an even stronger reliability.
If we do well in our follow -ups.
I think we should all ask ourselves:
Regarding this with working systematically and knowledge -based.
How do you work in my municipality?